KISHORE VISHAMBER MORDANI

A-5, 2nd Floor, Ananya Flats, Near Mangleshwar Mahadev, Road Towards Express Highway, Ghodasar, Maninagar, AHMEDABAD – 380050.

Cell# +91 - 99241 69975, +91 - 98240 86965.

Landline# +91 - 79 - 2538 2383.

Email: jollykishore@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 18th April, 1983.

SOFTWARE PROJECT MANAGER Top Performing and Multifunctional Project Manager

Over nine years' experience handling large scale of software projects in various domains with expertize in managing client expectations, requirements analysis & estimations, project planning & delivery, tracking & follow ups using Agile as well as traditional SDLC approach.

Offering – Leadership, organizational and customer management skills.

Objective – Seeking challenging position of software project management where managerial skills can be utilized to manage/direct various software and IT related projects efficiently emerging as excellent IT professional in the industry.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Programme Manager (Consultant – Technology Management), National Institute of Smart Government (NiSG), Gandhinagar, May, 2016 – Present.

Managing the key program of Digital Gujarat aimed at providing online Government Services to Citizens (G2C) – www.digitalgujarat.gov.in

- Managing citizen specific service identification & procurement from all government departments of Gujarat State.
- Passing over these services to the implementation agency: National Informatics Centre (NIC) in co-ordination with State Secretary – Information Technology.
- Tracking the development status through weekly status meeting
- Tracing & Resolving Impediments.
- Organizing National Level Event called National Summit on Innovations & Technology (NSIT) to support start-ups and creating platform for industry to showcase their products, platforms or technologies.

Onsite Project Manager (Managing Consultant, C7), eNoah iSolution India Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad, August 2014 – July 2015.

Single handedly managed entire client base of IIT Gandhinagar as onsite project manager.

- Coordinated with all departments to understand IT software needs and requirements of the client.
- Discussed specific needs and probable budget to build software as per clients' requirements.
- Managed a team of 40+ developers from offshore.
- Successfully executed planned GO Live of the educational ERP (Institute Management System) through ruthless execution as it was a strong penalty clause project.
- Inaugurated the ERP Solution in front of Board of Governance appointed by President of India.
- Also, managed entire Europe Account in capacity of delivery manager.

Manager, Specialized Services, Hitachi Consulting, Pune, September 2011 – March 2013.

End – to – End Software Project Management including requirement analysis, estimations and task delegation, project planning ,tracking, resolving impediments, team management as well as client management.

- Executed Projects in VIS & CRM Domain from U.S. Geography.
- Managed couple of mobile application development projects also, a few of them were at stake of organizational prestige wherein I resolved all impediments and got the project delivered in significantly short time span thereby restoring organization reputation in front of client.

Sr. Engineer (Software), Patni Computer Systems Ltd., Pune & Melbourne, December 2007 – September 2011.

Onsite Co-ordinator at Melbourne, Australia and Offshore Product Champion at Pune, India. Played various roles like Team Leader, Module Lead, Code Reviewer, Defect Prevention Representative (DPR) and Configuration Manager.

Executed Projects in Instrumentation Engineering Domain from APAC Geography.

- Contributed significantly in development of suite of applications for Instrumentation Engineering Industry.
- Developed a couple of features which as revealed by client were like one of the world's best feature that can be provided by any instrumentation engineering software.
- Streamlined processes & requirements flow between onsite & offshore.
- Received International Client Appreciation for my work as onsite co-ordinator.
- Executed Medical Analytics Projects for Japanese Geography for Hitachi High Technologies (HHT).

Software Engineer, TL – 5, TERA Informatics Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai, May 2007 - December 2007.

Involved into Software Development & Design, Client Management

Executed Projects in Health Care & Application Development in U.S. Geography.

Software Engineer, SaltRiver InfoSystems Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad, May 2006 - May 2007.

Involved into Software Development & Design, Client Management

 Executed Projects in Telecom, Security & Application Development in local as well as APAC Geography.

TECHNOLOGIES MANAGED

C#, VB.NET, C++/CLI, Managed C++, VC++ (Win32, MFC), Infragistics, Dev Express, ADO.NET Entity Framework, WCF, .NET Framework, ASP.NET MVC Razor, jQuery/javascript, Telerik, HTML 5, Android, iOS, Phone Gap, JAVA, PHP, MS – SQL, MS – Access.

EDUCATION

Masters of Business Administration (M.B.A.) in International Business (**Majors**) & Information Technology (**Minors**) with CGPA of 6.83/10 in 2013 from Amity School of Distance Learning (ASoDL) affiliated to Amity University, Noida

Bachelors of Engineering in Electronics & Communication with CPI of 6.58/10 in 2004 from A.D. Patel Institute of Technology (A.D.I.T.) affiliated to Sardar Patel University, VallabhVidyaNagar.

Professional Project Management Certification from SABCONS Management Consultants, Ahmedabad in October 2013.